what's up guys it's Mr b6000 here and
this is a mod review so basically it's
the boxy items mod so makes like your
pickaxes and all your items boxy if you
look at these they're all in box shape
and stuff see them shovel doesn't look
too much different it's one of those
mods it's just you know it's kind of
cool to look at and stuff and then it
adds Emerald boxy a and Lapis so it's
pretty cool to look at it's not one of
those things that actually help you you
can see you keep the old tools that's
what an old pickaxe that's a boxy
pickaxe uh where's the wood one see
there's the
difference it's what it looks like on
the
floor that's what it looks like in a
frame that's what it looks like in a
chest and this is what it looks like
when you hold it so they're pretty cool
I like them to make them there's a bunch
of recipes they're not too hard in case
you play in vanilla so there's a link to
download it in the description and in
the link it will also show you how to
craft everything I'm not going to go
through it all but basically use these
these and it's the same as the other
ones but it makes a boxy instead of
normal looking so that's basically it
short video straight to the point box
the item mod and hope you enjoy maybe go
download it trick your friends I don't
know you know play prank on them with
this somehow I don't know but anyways
thanks for watching